What is a failure
and how the failure becomes a good piece
I mean, it keeps revolving around what happened the first night
yes, let's go to the first night
because that for me is... that is a great piece
what happened was a great piece
and it didn't came from the stage
it came from the outside
and what happened to the context
when the eruption took place
Tell your witness story.
You're now a real witness.
where were you usually sitting when you were witnessing Crash Landing
on stage on the side
that night it was in a big sofa
I was sitting with Nadia Lauro
and euh...
we were watching basically
and were you visible to the audience?
yes.    yes.
so throughout you would be visible as someone in a sofa
watching... a piece
not to the whole
probably not the whole because it was quite of stage to the side
but at least half of the audience could see
and we weren't always there
and I wasn't always with Nadia
sometimes I was reall off stage
I just happened that at that time we were there
because it was in the way of working
there was kind of a...
there was a stage setting
with the square hole
over there (if I'm the audience)
on each side there were racks of clothes
that Nadia had proposed
she had gone through all the clothes of Théâtre de la Ville
the costume supply
and chose things that people could put on if they wanted
then there was the sofa
they could also go into the space or be not in the space
and there was the tree
that we used the first night
and euh... I don't remeber very well
what else there was on stage
and the music
ah there was Hahn
yes there were three musician places
with euh... Hahn and... I think
turntables
and what was his name...
David Linton
John Rose
Do you remember if you were announced in the program?
as a witness or as a participant?
as a witness
like this
whilst you're on stage as witness
do you perceive that as a role?
Sorry, what did you say?
You're a witness, but you're also on stage
in a sofa and... you know
You're really in the heat of the...
Does that become a role?
So it's part of the performance.
There is a moment I remember that I was sitting
with Nadia and she said
I feel so comfortable here