Myriam: OK.
Hahn: Now, what's this...
Myriam: I’m gonna explain a little,
because I talked to David about it more than I did to you.
So, Meg is going to make a book on Damaged Goods and her work,
and the book is going to consist of texts
that are more or less written by collaborators, artists,
and lots of interviews also.
They asked me to do something on Crash Landing,
actually the improvisation projects, so also Auf den Tisch.
It was an idea of Meg somehow to have a reunion,
with Christine and David,
because for most of the Crash Landings they were the three, say,
leading choreographers of Crash Landing.
Since Lisbon, since  Moscow
they have never really met the three of them.
So somehow Crash Landing is an end to their collaboration.
Somehow it marks even a series of endings,
and that was one of them.
So, the idea was that if they have a reunion and talk together
about the whole Crash Landing
in a very unedited way,
uninhibited, I would say,
to find out what it was and how they see its significance ten years later.
And I would do the reunion with them,
but I suggested that I wouldn’t speak with any of them,
with Meg, Christine nor David,
but that I would have like a round of interviews with the people
who were involved in some way or another.
That includes presenters, production managers, artists, musicians, audience.
And euh… I am going start actually my research,
because I need to have a research phase first, in October.
In that sense this conversation comes…
either it is a very good timing or either it is a very bad timing.
With a very good timing, I would mean, like it's a first exploration
in a more conversational way,
which I can then in October make a bit more profound,
when I really start researching.
So it could be like a teaser, an appetizer, a first…
opening the can actually... of worms.
Or it can be a bad timing if
if I feel that somehow I have not enough background information
to really trigger the right memory...
push the right memory buttons.
That's why it's good to the two of you
are here together, I feel.
David: Are there programs of any of them?
Myriam: Yes, well, there’s some videomaterial
although it's not so very well documented, Crash Landing.
David: Actually, of all things,
I wish I could just look at a program.
Just even to recreate musically who were the people in each one.
Hahn: Sometimes I even forget.
I was just talking about Vienna I guess with Meg
or somebody or maybe...
I forget who I was talking with.
I totally forgot about the Vienna musicians.
Hary De Wit, in Vienna, I remember very well.
But I do not remember a fourth,
if there was a fourth.
I don't even remember.
You see, I knew Harry De Wit beforehand.
He is a keyboardist and a percussionist, Dutch.
Hahn: Wasn’t there someone who played the saxophone or something?
Or guitar?
David : He also plays base, clarinet, and guitar and base
and tapdances.
He is just an all-round maniac,
god.
Can I do this? Leuven...
I can't spell them...
(David takes a piece of paper and a pen and starts writing down names ;
he is mapping the musical line up of each edition of Crash Landing,
starting with Leuven.)
Myriam: 1996.
Hahn: Ah, you see, already you remember... What do you do?
Ahh, kind of... I think...
Psychedelic underground.
(David points to the name of Music Transonic on the paper).